export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is the primary function of the Exosphere in our atmosphere?",
      option1: "Filtering air",
      option2: "Absorbing sunlight",
      option3: "Marking space boundary",
      option4: "Generating clouds",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What distinguishes the Thermosphere from other layers?",
      option1: "Low temperatures",
      option2: "Northern Lights",
      option3: "Thick air",
      option4: "Absence of satellites",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Why is the Mesosphere referred to as Earth's defense system?",
      option1: "Meteor showers",
      option2: "Cloud formation",
      option3: "Space debris protection",
      option4: "Night sky observation",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary role of the Stratosphere in protecting Earth?",
      option1: "Rain formation",
      option2: "Cloud dispersal",
      option3: "Ozone layer shield",
      option4: "Airplane cruising",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What activity characterizes the Troposphere?",
      option1: "Cloud formation",
      option2: "Ozone depletion",
      option3: "Satellite orbiting",
      option4: "Sunlight absorption",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which layer of the atmosphere experiences the highest temperatures?",
      option1: "Exosphere",
      option2: "Thermosphere",
      option3: "Mesosphere",
      option4: "Stratosphere",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What phenomenon occurs in the Thermosphere that is visually striking?",
      option1: "Rainbows",
      option2: "Thunderstorms",
      option3: "Northern Lights",
      option4: "Tornadoes",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What makes the Mesosphere significant in terms of meteoroids?",
      option1: "Meteor showers",
      option2: "Meteor formation",
      option3: "Meteor tracking",
      option4: "Meteorite collection",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which layer of the atmosphere acts as a shield against harmful solar radiation?",
      option1: "Exosphere",
      option2: "Thermosphere",
      option3: "Mesosphere",
      option4: "Stratosphere",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What activity is characteristic of the Troposphere's dynamic nature?",
      option1: "Rainfall",
      option2: "Space exploration",
      option3: "Star observation",
      option4: "Satellite deployment",
      ans: 1,
    },
  ];
  